Alien Warfare is a action, science fiction,
thriller film directed by Jeremiah Jones.
A team of Navy Seals investigates a mysterious science outpost only
to have to combat a squad of powerful alien soldiers.
Mike, played by Clayton Snyder.
Chris, played by David Meadows.
Thorpe, played by Scott C. Roe.
Isabella, played by Larissa Andrade.
Jonesy, played by Daniel Washington.
Marco, played by Tom DeNucci.
Alien: Earth is an American science fiction horror
television series created by Noah Hawley.
It is the first television series in the Alien franchise and is set
two years before the events of the 1979 film Alien.
The series stars Sydney Chandler, Alex Lawther, Essie Davis, Samuel Blenkin,
Babou Ceesay, Adarsh Gourav, and Timothy Olyphant in main roles.
Development for the series was reported to have begun in early 2019, with
Ridley Scott attached to executive produce for FX on Hulu.
It had started pre-production by April 2023, with Chandler cast in the lead role the
following month, and further casting taking place from July to November that year.
After principal photography was delayed due to the COVID-19 pandemic, production began
in July 2023 but was halted in August due to the 2023 SAG-AFTRA strike.
Filming resumed in April 2024 and ended in July that year.
Alien: Earth premiered on FX and FX on Hulu in the United States
and on Disney+ internationally on August 12, 2025.
In November 2025, the series was renewed for a second season.
The film explores themes of alien, u.s. navy seal, outpost, soldiers.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.